Welcome to the program, sit back in your seat Can lines scream at you, orders on repeat?
Every channel claims that they're the only guy But the more you're watching, the less you decide Scrolling through disasters, splash across the screen Men use that shuriken again, red and green Picking sides, a mob that trauma sold his batch The jeepin' has to bite, it never loved things that ain't
Truesty dating away, the facts get twisting every day.
Truesty day, what can we say?
When have fags got the rage?
Aight.
Talking heads with their agendas set.
Manufacturing outlets to collect.
West versus right, a false dichotomy Selling fear instead of bias deep Turn it off, tune it out There's something better to talk us out Than farnes and wise bears shouting out While the real loved ones go without
Truth D-Day, eating away, the facts get twisted every day.
Truth D-Day, what can we say, when headvines decorate?
Hey!
Truth DJ eating away, my back get twisted everyday.
Truth DJ, what can we say, when headlines drive the rage.
Turn down the static, reclaim your head, start questioning the narratives you've been fed.
Switch off the circus, step outside the frame, searching for meaning that isn't just a name.
No more distractions, break through the haze Put down the fear that keeps us all in chains No conversations, let actions remain It's up to us now to spark a change